# Ramzi Bouzaiene

Software engineering student Web Developer

+216 58275298

https://github.com/ramzibouzaiene

□ ramzibouzaiene00@gmail.com

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/ramzibouzaiene



# **PROFILE**

I am a software engineering student in my final year of studies, and i am a member/volunteer in certain clubs in the university. I'm truly passionate about software development since i was in high school. This passion carried me through my education at the university to develop myself and gain a more knowledge in software engineering field with some fundamentals in Artificial intelligence and Machine Learning. I was able to acquire a solid foundation during my three years of studies in development and software engineering, skills in which I particularly excelled during my studies. In addition, with internships in the field of web development.

# **EDUCATION**

► Higher Institute of Applied Science and **Technology of Sousse** 

Sept 2019 - Present

Bachelor's Degree in Software Engineering

Course Related: Machine Learning, Algorithm And Data Structures, Big Data, C Language, IT security, JAVA, SQL, SOA ...

#### **SKILLS**

► Front-End: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Angular, VueJs, JQuery

▶ Back-End : PHP , Laravel

DataBase: MySql, MongoDB, Oracle

Tools: VS Code, Git/GitHub, WordPress

Operating System : Windows/Linux

Others Languages: Python, Java, C++

# **LANGUAGE**

**ARABIC** FRENCH **ENGLISH** TURKISH

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

- ► Summer Internship at Nachd-IT (Jun 2021 - Sep 2021)
  - Building a website for the NACHD-IT company using the LARAVEL 7 Framework.
  - I completed all the tasks and I learned how to work with Laravel and PHP.
- ► Graduation Internship at Nachd-IT (Feb 2022 - Jun 2022)
  - Building a platform for my university club Platform dedicated to students of Issat Sousse University to improve their skills in different fields.
  - Improving the employability of future graduates through a program: Advice, support, training, certifications and networking.
- Capacity building for teachers: to better impact
- the employability of students.
- Define the activities, trainings, workshops, of the ISSAT Sousse 4C Center.

# **VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE**

- Media Assistant: Dynamic IssatSo (Nov 2020 - Jun 2021)
- Vice President: IoT & Data Science club issatso (Jan 2021 - Present)
- Student Ambassador :4C ISSAT SOUSSE (Mar 2021 - Present)
- ▶ Volunteer: Croissant Rouge Tunisien Club ISSATSo (Nov 2020 - Jun 2021)
- ► Head Of Sponsors Management: Hult Prize Higher Institute of Applied Science and Technology Sousse (Jul 2021 - Present)

#### **PROJECTS**

#### ▶ Website with LARAVEL

I created a simple website using PHP and the Framework LARAVEL.

Link:

https://github.com/ramzibouzaiene/Laravel-Web-Site

## ▶ Nachd-it Website

Creating a web site for the startup Nachd-it with Laravel.

i worked on both sides Frontend and Backend

Link:

https://github.com/ramzibou-zaiene/Nachd-IT-Website-Laravel-7-

## ▶ IOT & Data-Science Club Website

Building a website for our university club with my colleagues using HTML, CSS and PHP

Link: http://www.idsclub-issatso.com/

# Weather App With VueJs

Creating a simple Weather App With VueJS with an online API.

Link:

https://github.com/ramzibouzaiene/WeatherApp-With-VueJs

#### ▶ Team Generator With Angular

A simple app to learn how to work with angular 13

Link:

https://github.com/ramzibouzaiene/Team-Generator-With-Angular

# CRUD App With Laravel 8

Laravel 8 CRUD (Create, Read, Update, and Delete) operations with auth login and registration

Link:

https://github.com/ramzibouzaiene/CRUD-App-With-Laravel

# ► REST API With Laravel

REST API with auth using Laravel 8 and Sanctum and tested with Postman Link:

https://github.com/ramzibouzaiene/REST-API-Laravel-8